rapha.cc 2014-06-12

# Rapha | Privacy Policy

Rapha Racing Limited (“we”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our [Terms & Conditions](http://pages.rapha.cc/service/website-terms-conditions)) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. By visiting rapha.cc (“our site”) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Rapha Racing Limited of Imperial Works, Tileyard Rd, London N7 9AH.

### INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information you give us. You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site or on our social media pages or profiles, or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise.

Information we collect about you. With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information: technical information, e.g. about your browser or the device you use to access the site etc.; information about your visit, e.g. which website you clicked through to reach ours, lengths of visits to pages etc.

Information we receive from other sources. We work closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners and sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services) and may receive information about you from them.

### COOKIES

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse the site and also allows us to improve our site. See also our [Cookie Policy](http://pages.rapha.cc/service/cookies "Cookies").

### USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways:

Information you give to us. We will use this information to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us; to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about; to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. If you are a new customer, and we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the [order form OR registration form]);

Information we collect about you. We will use this information: to administer, operate and improve our site and ensure it is presented in the most effective manner; as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure; to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.

Information we receive from other sources. We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you and use it for the purposes set out above.

### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, including our US subsidiary Rapha Racing LLC and you should only give us your information if you consent to this.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: In the event that we sell or buy (or plan to sell or buy) any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If Rapha Racing LLC or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal, or in order to enforce or apply our [Terms & Conditions](http://pages.rapha.cc/service/website-terms-conditions "Website Terms & Conditions"). This includes

exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection.

### WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.

By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at enquiries@rapha.cc.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites. If you follow a link to of these websites, please note that those websites should have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.

### ACCESS TO INFORMATION

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. You may request from us a copy of personal data we hold on you subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs.

### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

### CONTACT

We welcome questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy. They should addressed to Rapha Racing Ltd, Imperial Works, Tileyard Rd.,London, N7 9AH or to enquiries@rapha.cc.
